Choudhury Vedaswarup (1) Featured

I am an Application Development Analyst with experience in Salesforce Development and Administration, Automation anywhere Tool, IBM Lotus Notes software, Business Process Automation, Automation Testing and Functional Testing.



Current Designation: Consultant Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 3 Months Current Company: Capgemini

Current Location: Bhubaneshwar Highest Degree:

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad, Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Salesforce, Salesforce.com, Salesforce CRM, SFDC, Visualforce, Apex, Triggers, Data Loader, Force.com, Sales Force Development, Business Development, Business Analysis, Requirement Analysis, Project Management,

Business Analytics, Business Process Op

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Summary

I am an Application Development Analyst with experience in Salesforce Development and Administration, Automation anywhere Tool, IBM Lotus Notes software, Business Process Automation, Automation Testing and Functional Testing. My daily activities include performing detailed analysis of business process requirements and provide appropriate system solutions; identify, interpret, validate and document customer requirements along with proposing the best possible solution with minimal impact, providing quick and effective support for reported issues and providing automation use cases and solutions to customers. I am an ardent learner and would prefer a challenging atmosphere which gives me a certain autonomy to experiment and leverage my skills.

Work Experience

Capgemini as Consultant Nov 2020 to Till Date

Accenture Solutions Pvt. Ltd as Application Development Analyst Apr 2017 to Nov 2020

I am an Application Development Analyst with experience in Salesforce Development and Administration, Automation anywhere Tool, IBM Lotus Notes software, Business Process Automation, Automation Testing and Functional Testing. My daily activities include performing detailed analysis of business process requirements and provide appropriate system solutions; identify, interpret, validate and document customer requirements along with proposing the best possible solution with minimal impact, providing quick and effective support for reported issues and providing automation use cases and solutions to customers. I am an ardent learner and would prefer a challenging atmosphere which gives me a certain autonomy to experiment and leverage my skills.

I have received multiple recognition and appreciation from my clients for my involvement in gathering business requirements and providing effective and time saving solutions.

I am also what you call "A Jack of all Trades", I like to learn multiple things like AWS, IoT, TOSCA, Desin Thinking, DevOps, Video Editing, Graphic Designing, Business Story telling and Event management. I need to perform multiple variety of tasks to keep me motivated and enthusiastic, which I do by planning and prioritizing my work using required tools.

I was called "A blessing in disguise" by my Managing Director (MD) for my energy and ideas which I used in organizing multiple Delivery Unit (DU) level events including flashmob, Annual Function, Team Building activities.

I also won Innovation Quiz and took art in multiple innovation contests in Accenture for which I received recognition points from my DU Lead.on 7th June, 2019

Pole To Win International as Trainee Test Engineer

Sep 2016 to Mar 2017

My role in this company was of Trainee Test Engineer, I was part of a team which used to perform multiple test execution, test cases preparation, sanity testing smoke testing, regression testing on mobile applications on multiple devices including iPhone(s), Android phones, tablets etc.

I was responsible handling daily calls with stake holders regarding test execution status, continuous co-ordination with application and SME's and Developers about reported bugs on bug tracker, preparing and sending weekly matrix, requirement trace-ability matrix, UAT scripts and test scripts.

We used to work on tools like JIRA, slack, Selenium and Appium

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Mechanical) from KIIT University, Bhuvaneshwar in 2016

PG: in 0

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
C, C++, Java, Lotus Script			
Python			
CATIA, JIRA, IBM Lotus Notes			
SharePoint, Selenium			
Appium			
Blue Prism, LEI and DIG			
Python		2020	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
AWS		2020	0 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
SALESFORCE		2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
RPA		2020	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Odia				

Projects

Project Title: Migrating LotusNotes Application To Salesforce

Client: Electrolux

Nature of Employment: Full Time **Duration: Oct 2018 - Sep 2020 Project Location: Hyderabad** Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Role: Sr. Programmer Team Size: 4

Skill Used: Salesforce, JavaScript, lotus script

1/22/2021

Project Details: Developed custom application, objects and fields, used apex triggers process builder lwc aura and lighting to build 3 applications. Used data loader and import data wizard for data migration. Used rest api and soap api for integration with third party

Project Title: Implementation of RPA Automation Anywhere in Electrolux engagement

Client: Electrolux

Nature of Employment: Full Time **Duration: Jun 2018 - Oct 2018 Project Location: Hyderabad** Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Role: Sr. Programmer Team Size: 5

Skill Used: Rpas, Automation Testing

Project Details: Description Established in 1919, Electrolux AB (commonly known as Electrolux) is a Swedish multinational home appliance manufacturer, headquartered in Stockholm It is consistently ranked the world's second largest appliance maker by units sold. Electrolux products sell under a variety of brand names (including its own) and are primarily major appliances.

Responsibilities:

Involved in discussion and documentation of business use cases suitable for Automation

Performed Automation Anywhere control room installation

Worked closely with Database owners to translate business process in to detailed design documents and team members to work on Bots accordingly

Designed, Developed and tested Bot tasks using Automation Anywhere.

Developed and documented configuration best practices create and maintain solution documentation.

Participated in day-to-day client interaction meetings and workshops.

Coordinated with database owners for optimisation of bots according to business need.

Project Title: Lotus Notes applications Development

Client: Electrolux

Nature of Employment: Full Time **Duration: Jan 2018 - Jun 2018 Project Location: Hyderabad** Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Role: Programmer Team Size: 5

Skill Used: Lotus Notes, Lotus Script, Lotus Notes Domino, Formula Language, Javascript

Project Details: Responsibilities:

Involved in requirement gathering of existing business practices and documenting As- Is business processes accordingly.

Designing and preparing functional specifications for required custom developments.

Configuration of Basic functions.

Handled the Tickets/Incidents as per the SLA.

Prepared weekly /Monthly status reports of Tickets/Incident.

Participated in day-to-day client interaction meetings and workshops. Coordinated with database owners for Customization/Enhancements.

Conducted training for end users on Lotus Notes functionalities and navigation through screens.

Interacted with end users as needed through Net meetings/phones/mails for resolving the tickets based on severity

Bug analysis with the technical team and business, regressing the resolved bugs.

Customization for the new business scenarios or changes to the existing business scenarios.

Assisted the user in migrating the existing Lotus Notes applications to new platform

Project Title: SharePoint, Lotus Notes application testing

Client: Electrolux

Nature of Employment: Full Time **Duration: Apr 2017 - Dec 2017 Project Location: Hyderabad** Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Role: Test Engineer Team Size: 3

Skill Used: Testing, Manual Testing, Software Testing, Manual, Automation Testing, Database Testing, QA Testing, Regression Testing, Advanced Excel, Business Process Analysis, Test Case Execution, Test Case Preparation, Test

Case Review, Test Case Design, User Management **Project Details: Responsibilities**

Preparing and Executing Test Cases, Test Scripts and UAT Scripts after analysing all the business requirements using Tricentis TOSCA.

Performing system test execution, and preparing defect tracker to capture all the gaps in the designed application

Preparing Weekly Dashboard for Testing team with the all testing updates and share with project management Preparing User Guides of newly developed SharePoint and Lotus Notes applications for customers

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No **Employment Status: Full time**